ah! Liulaoliu, this is Duoshe! No, wow, it’s so dangerous! This one is generous,
I hate pedicures here the most. You're stuck.
Wow! I hate this group of people the most, and they want to take over my nurse!
What I hate the most is when you watch Q C Q Yao Qi Yao, your uncle! Who taught you to play like this? oops!
You are true silver, you! I admit that the three of you are very skilled at multi-tasking.
He took away my nurse.
But I'm sorry, there are dodgy rats in the team, you are still too young. Hey, my feet are down,
My feet are down. Don't move yet. I'm hiding my hands. I'm hiding my hands. Here they are, right under my feet. Come up.
Don't move, don't move, don't move, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Man, holy shit! Can't stop! Ha ha ha ha! Three cats come to Iron Cat! Ha ha ha ha! Check it out,
Come on Iron Cat, come on Iron Cat! Is the boss fat? Is the boss fat? Is the boss fat?
Are you fat or not, boss? Ouch, so fat! Hurry! Ouch, A hit!
I think we can just go, this wave is already very fat.